cichic.com 2018-06-29

# Privacy & Security Policy

Cichic respects your concerns about privacy and value the relationship we have with you. This Privacy Notice describes the types of personal information we collect on our web site, how we may use that information, and with whom we may share it. Our Privacy Notice also describes the measures we take to protect the security of the information. In addition, we describe the choices you can make about how we use the information you provide to us. We also tell you how you can reach us to update your contact information, remove your name from our mailing lists, or ask any questions you may have about our privacy practices.

### Information we collect and how we use it

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form. While ordering our products we request the following personal information from you on our registration form: first and last name, billing/shipping address, telephone number, email address, username, password, credit card, and credit card number. This is the information we need to process your order. Your telephone number is required to complete the registration or order process, so that we can use it to contact you about your order if we need to. Your billing information is also used to ensure that the right person is charged for the merchandise ordered. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

To process transactions accurately and safely.  
To improve our website - we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.  
To improve customer service - your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.  
To send periodic emails - The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

**Note** : If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

### Cookies

When you visit our web site, your browser automatically sends us certain Internet-related information (such as the Internet Protocol (IP) address of the computer you’re using). We also may use cookies to better understand how visitors use our site.

Cookies are small text files that web sites often store on the computer hard drives of visitors to their sites. A cookie contains a unique code, which is used to recognize your computer when a user of your computer returns to a web site that was visited previously. Web beacons are Internet tools that help us determine, for example, whether a web site page has been viewed. We use cookies and Web beacons to enhance the online experience of our visitors and to better understand how our site is used. Cookies and Web beacons may tell us, for example, whether you have visited our site before or whether you are a new visitor.

The "help" portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to stop accepting new cookies, how to be notified when you receive a new cookie, and how to disable existing cookies. Remember, though, without cookies, you may not be able to take full advantage of all of our web site features.

### Information We Share

Cichic does not sell, rent, trade or otherwise disclose personal information about our web site visitors, except as described as follows: (i) if we are required to do so by law, (ii) in response to a request from law enforcement authorities or other government officials, or (iii) when we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to prevent physical harm or financial loss or in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual illegal activity.

We reserve the right to transfer any information we have about you in the event we sell or transfer all or a portion of our business or assets. Should such a sale or transfer occur, we will use reasonable efforts to try to direct the transferee to use personal information you have provided through this web site in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Notice.

### Links to Other Sites

Occasionally we provide links to other web sites for your convenience and information. These sites operate independently from our site and are not under our control. These sites may have their own privacy notices in place, which we strongly suggest you review if you visit any linked web sites. We are not responsible for the content of these sites, any products or services that may be offered through these sites, or any other use of these sites.

### Security

We maintain administrative, technical and physical safeguards to protect against unauthorized disclosure, use, alteration or destruction of the personal information in our possession. When you provide credit card information to make a purchase, we use the industry standard for Internet security -- Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology -- to help protect the information you provide. This Internet encryption standard scrambles data as it travels from your computer to our server. Please note, however, that perfect security does not exist on the Internet. You’ll know that you’re in a secure area of our web site when a "lock" icon appears on your screen and the "http" portion of our URL address changes to "https." The "s" stands for "secure."

### Children's Privacy

In accordance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998, Cichic's website or any of its contents are not directed towards children and do not knowingly collect personal information from children. Cichic is concerned with safeguarding children's privacy on the internet. If we receive knowledge that a child has registered without her or his parent or guardian's permission, we will remove all personal information about that person from our files.  
Secure Shopping By using our website, you consent to the usage and collection of information from you by Cichic. Any revisions or changes made to our Privacy Policy will be posted on our website for view in order that our users are informed of what information we collect, how it is used and under what circumstance, if any, is disclosed.

In accordance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998, Cichic's website or any of its contents are not directed towards children and do not knowingly collect personal information from children. Cichic is concerned with safeguarding children's privacy on the internet. If we receive knowledge that a child has registered without her or his parent or guardian's permission, we will remove all personal information about that person from our files.  
Secure Shopping By using our website, you consent to the usage and collection of information from you by Cichic. Any revisions or changes made to our Privacy Policy will be posted on our website for view in order that our users are informed of what information we collect, how it is used and under what circumstance, if any, is disclosed.

In accordance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998, Cichic's website or any of its contents are not directed towards children and do not knowingly collect personal information from children. Cichic is concerned with safeguarding children's privacy on the internet. If we receive knowledge that a child has registered without her or his parent or guardian's permission, we will remove all personal information about that person from our files.  
Secure Shopping By using our website, you consent to the usage and collection of information from you by Cichic. Any revisions or changes made to our Privacy Policy will be posted on our website for view in order that our users are informed of what information we collect, how it is used and under what circumstance, if any, is disclosed.

In accordance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998, Cichic's website or any of its contents are not directed towards children and do not knowingly collect personal information from children. Cichic is concerned with safeguarding children's privacy on the internet. If we receive knowledge that a child has registered without her or his parent or guardian's permission, we will remove all personal information about that person from our files.  
Secure Shopping By using our website, you consent to the usage and collection of information from you by Cichic. Any revisions or changes made to our Privacy Policy will be posted on our website for view in order that our users are informed of what information we collect, how it is used and under what circumstance, if any, is disclosed.

### Your Choices

If you would like to update your contact information or prefer not to receive certain communications from us (such as e-mail), please call or write us using one of the options provided below or visit Cichic.com.
